(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)EZ Aquarii A,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)EZ Aquarii B,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)EZ Aquarii C,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Procyon A.
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Those are the stars
that are nearest to me.
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Tra-la-la and fiddle-dee-dee.
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Oh, dear.
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)They really do be crazy.
(Joy(burping):)This lobster's good
on the way down
(Joy(burping):)and the way up.
(Leonard:)Should be-- it's
$30 a pound.
(Joy:)Hey, this is a date, right?
(Leonard:)Yep, it is.
(Joy:)73!
Whoa!
(Joy:)Excuse me, I have to go
to the little girls' room...
(Joy:)and take a wicked whiz.
(Bernadette:)I'll go with you.
(Joy:)Fair warning--
I had the asparagus.